aimeleondore.com 2014-05-17

# Aimé Leon Dore

At Aimé Leon Dore, we take each customer’s security and privacy seriously.

Please find below a detailed explanation of how information is shared with us through aimeleondore.com. Please note however that the following may not apply to information obtained through other websites or offline.

By choosing to visit our website and use the services provided therein, you are thereby accepting the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. If you disagree with such terms, we kindly invite you to refrain from visiting or using our website. Aimé Leon Dore reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy without notice and at any time, and any continued use of our site is an implicit acceptance of said changes.

Should you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to email us at customerservice@aimeleondore.com.

Personal Information

Aimé Leon Dore will only ask for the information needed and required to fulfill a customer’s request. When information is knowingly provided, such as when a customer places an order, fills out a form, signs up to a newsletter, etc., the following information may be retained: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date. Unless a customer opts not to receive any of our promotional communications, Aimé Leon Dore may use some information to contact a customer about sales and special offers, new products or site features, and the like.

Anonymous & Non-Personal Information

In order to better understand how customers use our website and thus provide them with better service, certain information may be collected that does not identify a customer individually, including but not limited to a customer’s IP address, browser information and reference site domain name upon their visit, as well as information about customer traffic patterns and site usage. We may use or share anonymous, or other non-personal information, such as the number of users who purchased a product or visited our site during a certain time period, in any other manner we feel is appropriate.

Use of Cookies 

Like most other websites, Aimé Leon Dore uses “cookies” which are files stored by a computer’s internet browser on its hard drive, in order to identify account holders, hold selections in a shopping cart when one leaves our site, and send e-mails to customers about their orders or any other shopping opportunities. Users may choose to disable cookies or be alerted when cookies are being sent. However, enabling cookies may provide for a better experience with our site, as certain aspects of the website may not function properly without cookies. In the event that a customer receives cookies from companies advertising on Aimé Leon Dore’s behalf, please note that these cookies are not subject to the present policy. 

Newsletters

Upon subscription to our weekly newsletter, Aimé Leon Dore collects customers’ email addresses. Other than third party agents expressly related to Aimé Leon dore (such as our marketing team, etc.), this information is not in any way, shape or form, shared with other third parties. If a customer no longer wishes to receive our newsletter at any time, instructions to unsubscribe are located within each newsletter.

Children’s Privacy

Any personal information from anyone we know to be under the age of 13 is not collected nor retained by Aimé Leon Dore. Aimé Leon Dore will not sell or ship any items ordered through the website directly to anyone we know to be under the age of 13. If a customer is under the age of 13, parental consent should be obtained prior to using our website. 

Use of Personal Information

As previously mentioned, a user’s personal information may be used to fulfill order requests, personalize user experience, improve customer service, and send periodic e-mails or newsletters. In the event that Aimé Leon Dore wishes to publicly use any of a user’s personal information, the user’s permission will be obtained prior to such use. 

Third-Party Websites or Agents

Third party websites, agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners who may assist in marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, fraud protection, and the like, may have access to your personal information, as needed to perform their functions, and are contractually obligated to protect your confidentiality and security. They may not use, sell, distribute or alter your data in any way other than to provide the requested services to our website.

Keeping Personal Information Secure

All personal information collected by our site is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In many instances, sensitive information such as credit card numbers, is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

To protect the security of your information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information submitted. When an order is placed through our site, the user must set up an account and create a username and password. 

If a user wishes to delete their account or change their password, or becomes aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of their password, please email us at customerservice@aimeleondore.com. While Aimé Leon Dore aims to do the necessary to ensure that each user’s personal information is secure once submitted, it is important to note that no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Linking To or From Other Web Sites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

Governing Law/Assignment

AimeLeonDore.com is published in the United States and is intended for users from the United States. U. S. law shall govern in any and all disputes. 

Policy Changes

Aimé Leon Dore has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Questions?

Any questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to our customer service department by emailing customerservice@aimeleondore.com
